Guide to the James O. Brown Associates Records
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series III: Author File
  - Gaige, Crosby (Box 128)
  - Gainsborough, Louis P. (Box 128)
  - Gaither, Gant (Box 128)
  - Galaida, Edward (Box 128)
  - Gale, Zona (Box 128)
  - Gallagher, Patricia (Box 128)
  - Gallas, Robert J. (Box 128)
  - Gambordella, Theodore L. (Box 128)
  - Ganley, Paul L. (Box 128)
  - Gardiner, Alexander (Box 128)
  - Gardiner, Wayne J. (Box 128)
  - Gardner, Leonard (Box 128)
  - Gardner, Nellie E. (Box 128)
  - Gardner, W. Dave (Box 128)
  - Garforth, John (Box 128)
  - Garland, Patrick (Box 128)
  - Garner, Leslie (Box 128)
  - Garnett, Edward Bernard (Box 128)
  - Garrett, Garet (Edward Peter Garrett) (Box 129)
  - Garrett, Leslie (Box 129)
  - Garrigues, Eduardo (Box 129)
  - Garvey, Sir Terence Willcocks (Box 129)
  - Gascoigne, Bamber (Box 129)
  - Gates, H.L. (Box 129)
  - Gathorne-Hardy, Jonathan (Box 129)
  - Gauer, Harold (Box 129)
  - Gauvreau, Emil (Box 129)
  - Gaver, Jack (Box 129)
  - Gaver, Jessyca Russell (Mrs. Jack) (Box 129)
  - Geen, Eric (Box 129)
  - Geer, Andrew (Box 129)
  - Geier, Paul E. (Box 129)
  - Gellens, Jay (Box 129)
  - Gelman, David (Box 129)
  - Gelzer, Jay (Box 129)
  - Gendel, Milton (Box 130)
  - Gene, Anthony (Box 130)
  - Georgas, Peter (Box 130)
  - George, Willis D. (Box 130)
  - Geraghty, Tom J. (Box 130)
  - Gerard, Rene H. Drioult (Box 130)
    ("Bassigny Gerrard")
  - Gerhardi, William Alexander (Box 130)
  - Gessner, Robert (Box 130)
  - Geyer, Donna. M (Box 130)
  - Gheladri, Robert, Jr. (Box 130)
  - Ghent, Henri & Alvin Smith (Box 130)
  - Gibb, Molly (Box 130)
  - Gibbon, Lewis Grassic (James Leslie Mitchell) (Box 130)
  - Gibbons, Floyd Phillips (Box 130)
  - Gibbons, Thomas J. (Box 130)
  - Gibbs, Anthony (Box 130)
  - Gibbs, George Fort (Box 130)
  - Gibbs, Mary Ann (Marjory Bidwell) & "Elizabeth Ford" (Box 130-131)
  - Gibson, Douglas Wood (Box 131)
  - Gibson, Gwen (Gwen Gibson Schwartz) (Box 131)
  - Gibson, Morgan (Box 131)
  - Gifford, Jessie Nebraska & Melvin Shestack (Box 131)
  - Gifford, James Parsons (Box 131)
  - Gignilliat, Leigh Robinson (Box 131)
  - Gilbert, Anthony (Lucy Beatrice Malleson) (Box 131)
  - Gilbert, Gustav M. (Box 132)
  - Gilbert, John (Box 132)
  - Gilbert, Michael Francis (Box 132)
  - Gilio, James (Box 133)
  - Gilkes, Lillian B. (Box 133)
  - Gill, Brendan & Dudley Witney (Box 133)
  - Gill, John (Box 133)
  - Gillan, Jim (Box 133)
  - Gillespie, Jane (Box 133)
  - Gillette, Don Carle (Box 133)
  - Gilliatt, Mary (Box 133)
  - Gilliatt, Penelope (Box 133)
  - Gillilan, Strickland (Box 133)
  - Gillmore, William J. (Box 133)
  - Gilman, Mildred (Mildred Wohlforth) (Box 134)
  - Gilmore, Richard A. (Box 134)
  - Gimbel, Bernard F. (Box 134)
  - Ginzburg, Natalia (Box 134)
  - Girard, Albert (Box 134)
  - Girouard, Mark (Box 134)
  - Girson, Rochelle (Box 134)
  - Giusti-Lanham, Hedy (Box 134)
  - Givens, Charles G. (Box 134)
  - Glad, Janet & Norman Lindsay (Box 134)
  - Gladdish, Kenneth (Box 134)
  - Gladstone, Myron J. & Juliana S. James (Box 134)
  - Glanville, Brian Lester (Box 135-136)
  - Glassford, Cora Carleton (Box 136)
  - Glazebrook, Mark (Box 136)
  - Glazer, Alan R. (Box 136)
  - Glenn, Taylor F. (Box 136)
  - Gluckman, Max (Box 136)
  - Godden, Rumer (Margaret Rumer Haynes Dixon) (Box 136)
  - Godfrey, Henry F. (Box 136)
  - Godwin-The Tony Godwin Memorial Trust (Box 136)
  - Gold, Herbert (Box 137-150A)
  - Gold, Judy (Box 151)
  - Gold, Melissa Dilworth (Mrs. Herbert) (Box 151)
  - Gold,-Sidney (Box 151)
  - Goldberg, David J. (Box 151)
  - Goldberg, Stan J. (Box 151)
  - Goldman, Emma (Box 151)
  - Goldman, Peter (Box 151)
  - Goldsborough, James Oliver (Box 151)
  - Golenpaul, Dan (Box 151)
  - Gollomb, Joseph (Box 151)
  - Goodchild, George (Box 151)
  - Goode, James A, & Norman E. Goldblatt (Box 151)
  - Goode, John (Box 151)
  - Goodkin, Sanford R. (Box 151)
  - Goodman, Daniel Carson (Box 151)
  - Goodman, Rita (Box 151)
  - Goodrich, Louis (Box 151)
  - Goodrich, Nancy (Box 151)
  - Goodwin, Hilda (Box 151)
  - Goodwyn, Frank (Box 151)
  - Goodyear, Donald R (Box 151)
  - Goolden, Barbara (Box 151)
  - Gordon, Colin (Box 152)
  - Gordon, Diana (Lucilla Creighton) (Box 152)
    ("Lucilla Andrews", "Joanna Marcus")
  - Gordon, Giles (Box 152)
  - Gordon, Harry (Box 152)
  - Gordon, Jan & Cora (Box 152)
  - Gordon, Patricia Neale (Box 152)
  - Gordon, Richard & Mary (Gordon Stanley Ostlere) (Box 152)
  - Gordon, Robert Lee (Box 152)
  - Gordon, Samuel G. (Box 152)
  - Gostenhofer, Charles (Box 152)
  - Gott, Richard (Box 152)
  - Gould, Shirley Joan & Shane (Box 153)
  - Gould, Tony (Box 153)
  - Gourse, Leslie (Box 153)
  - Goyen, William (Box 153)
  - Grace, Richard V. (Box 153)
  - Graeme, Sheila (Box 153)
  - Graham, Alastair (Box 153)
  - Graham, Frank (Box 153)
  - Graham, Frank & Ada (Box 153)
  - Graham, Sheilah (Box 153)
  - Granger, John T. (Box 154)
  - Granovetter, Bruce (Box 154)
  - Grant, Anne (Box 154)
  - Grant, Bruc e (Box 154)
  - Grant, Donald (Box 154)
  - Grant, Hugh Gladney (Box 154)
  - Grasso, George Allen (Box 154)
  - Graves, Alison (Box 154)
  - Graves, Ralph (Box 154)
  - Graves, Will (Box 154)
  - Gravina, Peter (Box 154)
  - Gray, Clyde (Box 154)
  - Gray, Dulcie (Dulcie Winifred Catherine Bailey Denison) (Box 154)
  - Gray, Edwyn (Box 154)
  - Gray, Philip H. (Box 154)
  - Gray, Robert M. (Box 154)
  - Gray, William S (Box 154)
  - Grbich, Ronald Ivan (Box 154)
    ("William Wingate")
  - Greasley, H.C. (Box 154)
  - Green, Abel (Box 154)
  - Green, Bert (Box 154)
  - Green, David (Box 154)
  - Green, Donald (Box 154)
  - Green, Harry (Box 154)
  - Green, Lewis W. (Box 154)
  - Greenberg, Henry Clay (Box 155)
  - Greene, Bert (Bertram Paule Greene) (Box 155)
  - Greene, Josiah E. (Box 155)
  - Greene, Laurence & Frank W. Brock (Box 155)
  - Greene, Ward (Box 155)
  - Greenwood, Charles T. (Box 155)
  - Greenwood, John (Box 155)
  - Greer, Germaine (Box 155)
  - Greer, Gordon G. (Box 155)
  - Grenier, Richard (Box 155)
  - Gresser, Julian (Box 156)
  - Gretton, Sir Peter William (Box 156)
  - Grey, Harry (Box 156)
  - Grey, Zane (Box 156)
  - Gridley, Charles O. (Box 156)
  - Grieg, Michael (Box 156)
  - Griffin, Bulkley Southworth (Box 156)
  - Griffin, Mary (Box 156)
  - Grimble, Ian (Box 156)
  - Grimes, John E. (Box 156)
  - Grimsley, Linda Genevieve Cravotta (Box 156)
  - Grimstead, Hettie (Box 156)
    ("Marsha Manning")
  - Grissim, John (Box 156)
  - Gronowicz, Antoni (Box 156)
  - Grooch, William Stephen (Box 156)
  - Gross, Edward (Box 156)
  - Gross, Jack, Jr. (Box 156)
  - Grossman, Harold (Box 156)
  - Gruen, John (Box 157)
  - Grumley, Michael (Box 157)
  - Grundy, Milton (Box 157)
  - Gruppe, Henry (Box 157)
  - Gude, J.C. (Box 157)
  - Guerite, Laura (Box 157)
  - Guerrier, Dennis & Joan Richards (Box 157)
  - Guinness, Bryan Walter (2nd Baron Moyne) (Box 157)
  - Guitar Player Productions (Eric Kriss) (Box 157)
  - Gunn, Elizabeth (Diana Maureen James Gunn, Mrs. Peter N.) (Box 157)
  - Guttmacher, Alan F. (Box 157)
  - Gwen, Edmund (Box 157)
  - Gwinner, Jean Q. (Box 157)
  - Haas, Albert, Jr., [À]on D. Jackson, & Arnold Rogow (Box 158)
  - Haas, John G. (Box 158)
  - Haas, Kurt (Box 158)
  - Hackenburg, Frederick L. (Box 159)
  - Hackett, Francis (Box 159)
  - Hackett, Marie G (Box 159)
  - Hackett, Paul (Box 159)
  - Hackett, Walter (Box 159)
  - Hadden, Hank (Box 159)
  - Hagood, Johnson (Box 159)
  - Haines, Lynn (Box 159)
  - Hainstock, Elizabeth G (Box 159)
  - Hale, Bryant M. (Box 159)
  - Halifax, Edward Frederick Lindley Wood, 2nd Viscount (Box 159)
  - Hall, Henry Noble (Box 159)
  - Hall, Lynn (Box 159)
  - Hallinan, Nancy & Robert Montgomery (Box 159)
  - Hallowell, Christopher L. (Box 159)
  - Halls, Geraldine M. (Box 159)
    ("Charlotte Jay")
  - Halperin, Donald & William McCune (Box 160)
  - Halverson, Marvin Pierce (Box 160)
  - Hamer-Jackson, Cornelia de Grandcourt (Mme. George) (Celesta Hamer-Jackson) (Box 160)
  - Hames, Robbye Lee (Box 160)
  - Hamilton, Cosmo (Cosmo Hamilton Gibbs) (Box 160)
  - Hamilton, Elizabeth (Box 160)
  - Hamilton, Gilbert Van Tassel & Kenneth MacGowan (Box 160)
  - Hamilton, Hale (Box 160)
  - Hamilton, Ian (Box 160)
  - Hamilton, William (Box 160)
  - Hamilton, William Winter (Box 160)
  - Hamlett, Robert (Box 161)
  - Hammond, Hilda Phelps (Box 161)
  - Hammond, Lorimer (Box 161)
    ("L.O. Remy")
  - Hammond, Sally (Box 161)
  - Hammond, William Churchill, III (Box 161)
  - Hammond Innes, Dorothy Mary Lang & Ralph (Box 161)
  - Hampton, Max (Box 161)
  - Hangen, Patricia (Mrs. Welles) (Box 161)
  - Hangen, Welles (Box 161)
  - Hankin, Francis (Box 161)
  - Hanley, Clifford (Box 161)
    ("Henry Calvin")
  - Hanley, Eve (Box 161)
  - Hanson, Earl Parker (Box 162)
  - Hanson, Gillian (Box 162)
  - Hanson, Lawrence & Elizabeth (Box 162)
  - Hapgood, David & Meridan Bennett (Box 162)
  - Hardin, C. Robert (Box 162)
  - Hardy, Frank (Francis Joseph Hardy) (Box 162)
  - Hare, Tracy B. (Box 163)
  - Hargrove, John (Box 163)
  - Harkness, Ruth (Mrs. William H., Jr.) (Box 163)
  - Harlech, Pamela Colin Ormsby Gore, Baroness (Box 163)
  - Harman, Nicholas (Box 163)
  - Harper, Karen S. (Box 163)
    ("Charlotte Loher")
  - Harriman, Joseph Wright (Box 163)
  - Harrington, Curtis (Box 163)
  - Harris, Barbara S. (Box 163)
  - Harris, John (Box 164)
    ("Max Harris", "Mark Hebden", "Max Hennessey")
  - Harris, Kenneth David (Box 165)
  - Harris, Marilyn (Marilyn H. Springer) (Box 165)
  - Harris, Roger Williams (Box 165)
  - Harris, Stuart (Box 165)
  - Harrison, Francis Burton & Doria (Mrs. Francis Burton) (Box 165)
  - Harrison, Mary Roberts (Box 165)
  - Harriss, R.P. (Box 165)
  - Harrisson, Tom (Box 165)
  - Hart-Davis, Duff & Jimmy Chipperfield (Box 165)
  - Hartney, Harold Evans 8s George W. Sutton (Box 165)
  - Hasey, John F. (Box 166)
  - Hastings, Macdonald (Box 166)
  - Hastings, Max (Box 166)
  - Hatch, Leonard (Box 166)
  - Hatcher, Harry (Box 166)
    ("Glenn Riley")
  - Hattersley, Ralph (Box 166)
  - Hauck, Walter (Box 166)
  - Hauser, Marianne (Box 166)
  - Haussmann, Veronica G. Murray (Box 166)
  - Haverstock, Mary Sayre (Box 166)
  - Hawes, Elizabeth (Box 166)
  - Hawes, Hampton (Box 166)
  - Hawke, David Freeman (Box 166)
  - Hawley, Hudson (Box 166)
  - Hawthorne, Julian & Edith Garrigues Hawthorne (Mrs. Julian) (Box 166)
  - Hawthorne, Ruth A. (Mrs. William Almon Wolff) (Box 166)
  - Hayden, Sterling (Box 166)
  - Hayden, Torey L. (Box 166)
    ("K. Thomas Rainer")
  - Hayes, Frank L. (Box 166)
  - Hayes, Joseph (Box 167-180)
  - Hayes, Raphael (Box 181)
  - Hayes, Teddy (Box 181)
  - Haynes, Kenneth A. (Box 181)
  - Hays, Arthur Garfield (Box 181)
  - Hays, William H. (Box 181)
  - Haythorne, John (Box 181)
  - Headland, Helen (Box 181)
  - Healy, Tim & Y.K. Smith (Box 181)
  - Hearn, Olive (Box 181)
  - Heath, Catherine (Box 181)
  - Heaton, Mary (Box 181)
  - Heckert, Eleanor L. (Box 181)
  - Heckheimer, Harry (Box 181)
  - Heckman, Hazel (Box 181)
  - Heed, Ruth Martha Byers (Box 181)
  - Heermance, Clayton J. & Carolyn Collyer (Box 181)
    ("Lyn Collyer")
  - Heffernan, John Vincent (Box 181)
  - Hein, Adeline Hawkes (Box 181)
  - Heinemann, Leopold (Box 181)
  - Held, Anna, Jr. (Box 181)
  - Hellman, Sam (Box 181)
  - Helm, Carl (Box 181)
  - Helm, Edith Benham (Box 181)
  - Helm, Thomas William, III (Box 181-182)
  - Helms, Svend Walter (Box 183)
  - Hemingway, Leicester & Sir Anthony Banks Jenkinson (Box 183)
  - Hemmingway, William (Box 183)
  - Henderson, Marjorie (Box 183)
  - Hendrix, Hedda (Box 183)
  - Henfrey, Colin (Box 183)
  - Henley, Constance Jordan (Box 183)
  - Henley, Ida G (Box 183)
  - Henney, Elizabeth (Box 183)
  - Henning, Ruth Margaret Barth (Box 183)
  - Henriques, E, Frank (Box 183)
  - Henshaw, Richard (Box 183)
  - Her Majesty's Stationery Office (Box 183)
  - Herbert, Francis Xavier (Box 183)
  - Herendeen, Chase & Anne (Box 183)
  - Herlihy, James Leo (Box 183)
  - Herman, Helen (Box 183)
  - Hernon, Peter (Box 183)
  - Herold, Don (Box 183)
  - Herrick, Elinore Morehouse & Geraldine Sartain (Box 183)
  - Herrin, Lamar (Box 183)
  - Hertz, Alexander (Box 183)
  - Hertzberg, G.R.R. (Box 183)
  - Hesky, Olga (Box 183)
  - Hess, John (Box 184)
  - Heuer, Kenneth John, Richard D, Adams, Flora Armitage, & George Selden Thompson (Box 184-185)
    ("Kenneth K. Richard", "Dick Richmond")
  - Hewes, Thomas (Box 185)
  - Hewitt, Margaret (Box 185)
  - Heywood, Anne (Anne Heywood Reid) (Box 185)
  - Heywood, Johnson (Box 185)
  - Hickok, Lorena A. (Box 185)
  - Higdon, Victor (Box 185)
  - Higgins, Anne (Box 185)
  - Higgins, Marguerite (Box 185)
  - Higgins, Ronald T. (Box 185)
  - High, Stanley Hoflund (Box 185)
  - Higham, Charles (Box 186-187)
    ("Patrick Boyd")
  - Hildreth, Howard Prescott (Box 188)
  - Hill, C. Richard (Box 188)
  - Hill, Christopher (Box 188)
  - Hill, Christopher John Ridley (Box 188)
  - Hill, James Lockette (Box 188)
  - Hill, R. Lance (Box 188)
  - Hill, Susan Elizabeth (Box 189)
  - Hilliard, Edwin (Box 189)
  - Hillsmith, Fannie (F. Hillsmith Welchman) (Box 189)
  - Hilton, John Buxton (Box 189)
  - Hine, Al & Sesyle Joslin Hine (Box 189)
  - Hines, Barry (Box 189)
  - Hinternhoff, John F. (Box 189)
  - Hinton, Walter (Box 189)
  - Hintze, Naomi A., Jon Hintze, J. Gaither Pratt, Robert C. Rogers, Jr., & Peter H. van der Linde (Box 189-190)
  - Hippard, Ruth Ridenour (Mrs. George) (Box 191)
  - Hirsch, Richard (Box 191)
  - Hiscocks, Charles Richard (Box 191)
  - Hitchcock, Raymond John (Box 191)
  - Hitchings, Beverly (Box 191)
  - Hivnor, Robert (Box 191)
  - Hoan, Daniel Webster (Box 191)
  - Hoare, Rodney Pelham (Box 191)
  - Hobbs, Jack Edison (Box 191)
  - Hobbs, Lisa (Box 191)
  - Hobbs, Robert L. (Box 191)
  - Hobhouse, Christina (Box 191)
  - Hobhouse, Leonard T. (Box 191)
  - Hobson, Frances (Box 191)
  - Hobson, Polly (Julia Evans) (Box 191)
  - Hochschild, Mrs Walter (Box 191)
  - Hodgman, Ann (Box 191)
  - Hoe, Susanna Leonie (Box 191)
  - Hoffman, Arthur Sullivant (Box 191)
  - Hoffman, Betty (Box 191)
  - Hoffman, Dorothy Karr (Box 191)
  - Hoffman, Paul Gray (Box 191)
  - Hoffstrom, Virginia (Box 191)
  - Hofmekler, Ori (Box 191)
  - Hogbin, Stephen (Box 191)
  - Hohler, Sir Thomas Beaumont (Box 191)
  - Holden, Barry Barfield (Box 191)
  - Holland, Isabelle C. (Box 192)
  - Holland, John (John Holland Smith) (Box 192)
  - Holland, Richard D. (Box 192)
  - Holland, Robert (Box 192)
  - Holland, Thelma Besant (for Vyvyan Beresford Holland) (Box 192)
  - Hollander, Phyllis (Box 192)
  - Hollander, Ron (Box 192)
  - Hollander, Zander (Box 192)
  - Hollinger, Carol (Box 192)
  - Hollywood, Daniel (Box 192)
  - Holman-Hunt, Diana (Diana D. Cuthbert) (Box 193)
  - Holme, Enid C.E. (Box 193)
    ("Diane Saryon" & "Charles Francis Bergin")
  - Holmes, George Sanford (Box 193)
  - Holmes, Taylor (Box 193)
  - Holt, Rackham (Margaret Van Vechten Saunders Holt) (Box 193)
  - Holtby, Winifred (Box 193)
  - Holzman, Phyllis (Box 193)
  - Holzworth, John Michael (Box 193)
  - Home, Charles Cospatrick Douglas- (Box 193)
  - Hone, Basil (Box 193)
  - Honeycutt, Ann (Box 193)
  - Hooker, John (Box 193)
  - Hoopes, Clement R. (Box 194)
  - Hoopes, Ned Edward & Elsa Lanchester (Box 194)
  - Hooper, Walter & C.S. Lewis (Box 195)
  - Hoover, Herbert Clark (Box 195)
  - Hope, Earl R. (Box 195)
  - Hopkins, Arthur Melancthon (Box 195)
  - Hopkins, Mary Alden (Box 195)
  - Horine, William W. (Box 195)
  - Home, Alistair Allan (Box 195)
  - Home, Donald (Box 195)
  - Hornibrook, William Harrison (Box 195)
  - Horton, Fane Merriman (Box 195)
  - Horton, Millard C. (Box 195)
  - Hough, Graham Goulder (Box 195)
  - Hough, Richard Alexander (Box 195)
    ("Bruce Carter")
  - Hovick, Rose E. Thompson (Box 195)
  - Howard, Oscar (Box 195)
  - Howard, Roy Wilson (Box 195)
  - Howarth, David Armine (Box 195)
  - Howe, Helen (Box 196)
  - Howe, John P. (Box 196)
  - Howe, Quincy (Box 196)
  - Howe, Robin (Box 196)
  - Howell, Barbara (Box 196)
  - Howell, Mary (Mrs Trevor) (Box 196)
  - Howland, Hewitt H. (Box 196)
  - Howley, Frank Leo (Box 196)
  - Hoyt, Waite C. (Box 196)
  - Hubank, Roger (Box 196)
  - Hubbard, Kin (Frank McKinney) (Box 196)
  - Hubbard, Richard Henry (Box 196)
  - Hubbard, Robert (Box 196)
  - Hubbard, Wynant Davis (Box 196)
  - Hubbert, Cecil Foscue (Box 196)
  - Hubert, Richard Lynn & Sam Berman (Box 196)
  - Hubert, William Mack (Box 196)
  - Huddleston, Sylvia Harlan (Box 196)
  - Hudson, John Paul (Box 196)
    ("John Francis Hunter")
  - Huff, Charles H. (Box 197)
    ("Drexel Drake")
  - Huff, Jane C. (Mrs. James A.) (Box 197)
  - Hughes, A. Daniel (Box 197)
  - Hughes, David (Box 197)
  - Hughes, Jack (Box 197)
  - Hughes, John L. (Box 197)
  - Hughes, Peter Tuesday (Box 197)
  - Hughes, Spike (Patrick Cairns Hughes) & Charmian Joyce Hughes (Box 197)
  - Hull, Walter H. & John F. Sinclair (Box 197)
  - Hulme, Jean C. (Box 197)
  - Hummel, George Frederick (Box 197)
  - Humphrey, Lucius (Box 197)
  - Hundley, Joan Martin (Box 197)
  - Hungerford, Edward (Box 197)
  - Hunsucker, Mrs Robert T. (Box 197)
  - Hunt, Sir David Wathen Stather (Box 197)
  - Hunt, Frazier (Box 197)
  - Hunt, H. Dunham (Box 197)
  - Hunt, John Clinton & Chantal Hunt (Box 198-199)
  - Hunt, Sydney (Box 199)
  - Huntington, Hester G. (Box 199)
  - Huntoon, Mary (Box 199)
  - Hurlbut, James W. (Box 199)
  - Hum, Philip D. (Box 199)
  - Hurst, Fannie" (Box 199)
  - Hurwood, Bernhardt J. (Box 199)
  - Hutchins, Anne S. (Box 200)
  - Hutchins, Robert May nard & Maude Phelps McVeigh Hutchins (Mrs. Robert M.) (Box 200)
  - Huth, Angela (Box 200)
  - Hyde, Douglas (Box 200)
  - Hyde, Harford Montgomery (Box 200)
  - Hyland, Ann (Box 200)
  - Hyman, Mac (McKenzie Hooks Hyman) (Box 201-203)
  - Ibbotson, Eva Maria Charlotte Michele Wiesner (Box 204)
  - Iglehart, David Stewart (Box 204)
  - Ike, Vincent Chukwuemeka (Box 204)
  - Imrey, Frank von (Box 204)
  - Ingalls, Laura H. (Box 204)
  - Ingalls, Rachel (Box 204)
  - Inglis, Brian St. John (Box 204)
  - Inglis, Ruth (Box 204)
  - Ireland, Alleyne (Box 204)
  - Ireland, David (Box 204)
  - Irvin, Rea (Box 204)
  - Irvine, R.R. (Box 204)
  - Irwin, Wallace (Box 204)
  - Irwin, William Dave (Box 204)
  - Ischlondsky, N.E. (Box 204)
  - Ishlon, Deborah (Box 204)
  - Israels, Josef, II (Box 204)
  - Iwasa, Kiyoshi (Box 204)
  - Jackman, Stuart (Box 205)
  - Jackson, Dale & Forest O'Brine (Box 205)
  - Jackson, Don D. (Box 205)
  - Jackson, Edwina & Marie Armstrong Essipov (Box 205)
  - Jackson, James Turner (Box 205)
  - Jackson, Priscilla (Box 205)
  - Jackson, Sara (Box 205)
  - Jackson, Walter (Box 205)
  - Jacobs, Paul & Joyce Goldstein (Box 205)
  - Jacot, Michael (Box 205)
  - Jaeckel, Theodore R. (Box 205)
  - Jaeger, Theodore F. (Box 205)
  - Jagger, Brenda (Box 205)
  - James, Dorothy Parsons (Box 205)
  - James, Francis (Box 205)
  - James, Julia (Box 205)
  - Jameson, Betty (Box 205)
  - Jameson, Haute Booth Tarkington (Box 205)
  - Jarrett, Derek (Box 206)
  - Jarvis, Fred G. & Robert Merrill (Box 206)
  - Jay, Antony R. (Box 206)
  - Jay, Peter (Box 206)
  - Jeneid, Michael (Box 206)
  - Jenkins, Burris A. (Box 206)
  - Jenkins, Elizabeth (Box 206)
  - Jenkins, Gwyn (Box 206)
  - Jenkins, Lyll Becerra de (Box 206)
  - Jenkins, Peter (Box 206)
  - Jennings, C. Robert (Box 207)
  - Jennings, Walter P. (Box 207)
  - Joachim, Joachim George (Box 207)
  - Johns, Clondesley (Box 207)
  - Johnson, Arthur H. (Box 207)
  - Johnson, Cecil C. (Box 207)
  - Johnson, Edward (Box 207)
  - Johnson, Bail Richard (Box 207)
  - Johnson, Gerald White (Box 207)
  - Johnson, Harry C. (Box 207)
  - Johnson, Hugh S. (Box 207)
  - Johnson, Miriam J. (Box 207)
  - Johnson, Marion (Box 207)
    ("Georgiana Masson")
  - Johnson, Nora (Box 207-208)
  - Johnson, Pamela Hansford (Box 208)
  - Johnson, Stanley Patrick (Box 208)
  - Johnson, Suzanne E. (Box 208)
  - Johnson, Thomas Marvin (Box 208)
  - Jolas, Jacques (Box 208)
  - Jolas, Maria (Mme. Eugene) (Box 208)
  - Jolly, William P. (Box 208)
  - Jonas, Carl (Box 209)
  - Jones, Guy Pearce (Box 210)
  - Jones, John R. (Box 210)
    ("John Dalmas")
  - Jones, Mervyn (Box 210)
  - Jones, Richard (Box 210)
  - Jones, Robert Tyre, Jr. (Box 210)
    ("Bobby Jones")
  - Jones, Stead (Thomas E. Jones) (Box 210)
  - Jordan, Evelyn (Box 210)
  - Jordan, James B (Box 210)
  - Joyce, James Avery (Box 210)
  - Jullian, Philippe (Box 210)
  - Jute, Andre (Box 210)
    ("Andrew McCoy")
  - Kahn, Albert E. & Michael Sayers (Box 211)
  - Kaiper, Dan & Nan (Box 211)
  - Kalep, Elvy (Box 211)
  - Kaltenborn, Hans Von (Box 211)
  - Kammer, J. Kerry (Box 211)
  - Kamp, Mary Ann (Box 211)
  - Kampf, Herbert A. (Box 211)
  - Kamrass, Geraldine Swados (Box 211)
  - Kane, Robert S (Box 211)
  - Kantor, Tim (Box 211)
  - Kapurthala, Brinda, Maharani of (Box 211)
  - Karger, Alfred Gus (Box 211)
  - Karp, Richard & Harvey R. Shapiro (Box 211)
  - Karp, Walter B. & Harvey R. Shapiro (Box 211)
  - Karr, Harold S. (Box 211)
  - Karraker, John (Box 211)
  - Kaslov, Steve (Box 211)
  - Kata, Elizabeth (Box 211)
  - Kauffman, George (Box 211)
  - Kauffman, Reginald Wright (Box 211)
  - Kaufman, Lenard (Box 211)
  - Kay, Eva (Box 212)
  - Kaye, Joseph (Box 212)
  - Keating, Micheline (Box 212)
  - Keegan, William (Box 212)
  - Keeler, Oscar B. (Box 212)
  - Keenan, Edward T. (Box 212)
  - Keene, Peter (Percy Francis Keene) (Box 212)
  - Keep, John L.H. (Box 212)
  - Kehoe, James (Box 212)
  - Keinzley, Frances (Box 212)
  - Keith, Don Lee (Box 212)
  - Kelder, James (Box 212)
  - Kellems, Vivien (Box 212)
  - Keller, Karl (Box 212)
  - Kelley, Sally (Box 212)
  - Kelly, James F (Box 213)
  - Kelly, John Eoghan (Box 213)
  - Kelly, Mary (Box 213)
  - Kemp, Harry Hibbard & Maud M. Merrill (Box 213)
  - Kempton, Murray (Box 213)
  - Keneally, Thomas Michael (Box 213)
  - Kennedy, John Castillo (Box 214)
  - Kennedy, Margaret (Lady Davies) (Box 214)
  - Kennedy, Mary (Box 214)
  - Kent, Walter (Box 214)
  - Keogh, Theodora (Theodora Keogh O'Toole) (Box 214)
  - Kerns, Frances Casey Jobe (Box 214-215)
  - Kerr, John (Box 215)
  - Kerwood, Elizabeth S. (Box 215)
  - Ketcham, Charles Brown (Box 215)
  - Key, Ted (Box 215)
  - Keyes, Edward (Box 215)
  - Keyserlingk, Count Hermann Alexander von (Box 215)
  - Kihn, W. Langdon (Box 216)
  - Kilborn, Orson (Box 216)
  - Kilbourne, Fannie (Box 216)
  - Kilbracken, John Raymond Godley, 3rd Baron (Box 216)
  - Kilby, Clyde S. (Box 216)
  - Kiley, John Cantwell (Box 216)
  - Kilgallen, Dorothy (Box 216)
  - Kilgore, Katherine (Box 216)
  - Kilmartin, Angela (Box 216)
  - King, Caroline Blanche Campion (Box 216)
  - King, Elizabeth M. (Box 216)
  - King, Elsie S. (Box 216)
  - King, Florence (Box 216)
    ("Eleanor Desmond", "Jerome Foster", "Ruding Upton King", "Louise Preston", "Ellen Upton", "Constance Upton")
  - King, Henry (Box 216)
  - King, Julius (Box 216)
  - King, Preston (Box 216)
  - King, William C. (Box 216)
  - Kingsford-Smith, Sir Charles (Box 216)
  - Kingsley, Myra & Percy Finch (Box 216)
  - Kingsmill, Hugh (Hugh Kingsmill Lunn) (Box 216)
  - Kipling, Marie (Box 216)
  - Kiriline, Louise Flach de (Box 216)
  - Kirkland, Jack & Ersking Caldwell (Box 216)
  - Kirkup, James (Box 216)
  - Kirsch, Charlotte L. (Box 216)
  - Kiser, Samuel E. (Box 217)
  - Klamkin, Charles & Elsie Fetterman (Box 217)
  - Klamkin, Lynn (Box 217)
  - Klamkin, Marian (Box 217-219)
  - Kling, Samuel G. (Box 220)
  - Kluger, Phyllis (Box 220)
  - Khappert, Jan (Box 220)
  - Kharr, Catherine S. (Box 220)
  - Knight, Clayton (Box 220)
  - Knight, David (Box 220)
  - Knight, Gladys (Box 220)
  - Knight, Vick (Box 220)
  - Knowles, Frances (Box 220)
  - Koenigsberg, Moses (Box 220)
  - Kohn, Harry Imre (Box 220)
  - Komroff, Manuel (Box 220)
  - Konjolka, Tanya K. (Box 220)